

Md Shoriful Islam

Frontend Developer

Sector # 18, Uttara, Dhaka 123001755247316

About Me

I'm Shoriful Islam, a Frontend Developer with good knowledge in html5, css3, sass, less, javascript, jquery, Wordpress (Basic), Photoshop and Figma. Currently I'm working with Themexe and willing to work remotely for a great company like you.

My best chances in this company is that I'm going to take new challenges and learn exciting things as I'm a fast learner. I hope I will do my best with my expertise and will become a perfect guy with your greatness and kindness.

Work experience

Frontend Web Developer

2019 - Present

Themeforest

https://themeforest.net

Frontend Developer

2019 - Present

Themexe

https://themeforest.net/user/themexe/portfolio

Education

Bachelor of Arts (B.A Honor's)

2015 - Present

Government Bera Degree College

HSC 2013 - 2014

Government Bera Degree College

Overall GPA: 3.60/5.00

SSC 2011 - 2012

Panchuria Dakhil Madrasah

Overall GPA:3.75/5.00

Skills

HTML5/CSS3/SASS/LESS

JavaScript/jQuery

WordPress/PHP

Dashboard Templates

Portfolio

https://themeforest.net/user/themexe/portfolio

- 1. http://emran-khan.com/drivel/
- 2. http://emran-khan.com/seokart/
- 3. http://emran-khan.com/picdrive/
- 4. https://emran-khan.com/transgo/
- 5. https://goo.gl/p4muJQ
- 6. https://goo.gl/nfRnbz

Reference

Name: Emran Khan

Position: Frontend Developer

Address: Uttara Dhaka, Bangladesh Webste: http://emran-khan.com

Created with 🔽 VisualCV